Observa la imagen muestra.jpg
Imagina la estructura
Piensa la responsividad: 1 columna en celular 2 columnas en sm y 4 en lg, para los Cards de servicios
Busca una fuente Google e intégrala
Integra colores a la paleta de Tailwind CSS
Integra textos e imágenes
Revisa el comportamiento responsivo
Al terminar comprime y sube tu proyecto


******************


Rooms
Food
Drink
Offers
Explore
Gallery
Info
Book
 
Contact

escape on the path less travelled...

This 18th century coaching inn stands next to the Saxon church in the picturesque village of Romaldkirk near Barnard Castle amidst the stunning countryside of Teesdale where the Durham and Yorkshire dales meet in spectacular rural landscapes.

Rooms
Fourteen very comfortable bedrooms with character, charm and splashes of luxury.
View 'Rooms'

Food
This is what we are about; keeping it local, adding some interest and doing it well.
View 'Food'

Drink
A true country bar with bags of character, a huge open fire and great food and drink.
View 'Drink'

Offers
Seasonal short breaks, special events and late deals to hopefully tempt you along.
View 'Offers'

The Rose & Crown at Romaldkirk, Barnard Castle, Co. Durham, DL12 9EB | (+44) 0-1833 650213 | hotel@rose-and-crown.co.uk
Company registration number – 8198113. Please read our Privacy policy and Terms & conditions
